WILLIAN INACIO GONÇALVES

w.goncalves91@gmail.comgithub.com/WillianGoncalves

**** +55 22 998860313

Rio de Janeiro, Brasil

in linkedin.com/in/willian-goncalves

I started studying Information Systems in a 3-year technical course in the Federal Center of Technologycal Education. As soon as I finished the technical course, I entered a Bachelor's degree in Information Systems, at the same institution. At that time, I was co-author of a short article published in Brazilian Symposium on Multimedia and the Web (WebMedia), the main event of the theme in Brazil.

I have been working with software development since 2012. In this period I have worked in desktop, web and mobile projects, but int the last years, I have focused on web development and on developing skills like automated deployment and tests.

Today I continue to study with online courses, seeking to improve my skills.

EXPERIENCE

Web Developer

O2 Filmes

Cotober 2018 — Ongoing

♀ Remote

- Developing and maintaining backend using Ruby on Rails
- Developing and maintaining frontend using React
- Writing integration and unit tests using Webdriver
- Version Control using Git
- Tasks management using Trello
- Working by Scrum framework

.NET Developer

Prion

September 2018 — October 2018

Rio de Janeiro, Brazil

- $-\,$ Developing and maintaining software using .NET Framework and SQL Server
- Version Control using Git
- Tasks management using Jira

Web Developer

Datahex

May 2017 — August 2018

- Rio de Janeiro, Brazil
- Developing and maintaining backend using Node
- Developing and maintaining frontend using Angular
- Developing mobile apps using Ionic
- Version Control using Git
- Tasks management using Trello
- Working by Scrum framework

.NET Developer

R₂MS

February 2013 — January 2017

Rio de Janeiro, Brazil

SOFTSKILLS



PROFESSIONAL SKILLS

JAVA
C#
SQL
Git

STRENGTHS

· Development



· Development Tools – DB



Development Tools – IDE



- Developing and maintaining desktop applications using .NET Framework
- Developing and maintaining web sites using Node
- Version Control using Git

PROJECTS

digitalnakomora.hr

King ICT d.o.o.

- September 2018 March 2019
- **Q** Zagreb, Croatia
- The platform bring all the important information for entrepreneurs such as: macroeconomic indicators at the level of Croatia and individual counties, average monthly net wage, registered unemployment rate, inflation, number of active business entities and many more. Business entities can be searched by name, responsible persons or statistics of activity and can be compared with other entities.
- Techs: ASP.NET MVC, Entity Framework, ReactJS and SQL Server

Electronic Toll Collection

King ICT d.o.o.

- March 2019 August 2019
- **♀** Zagreb, Croatia
- · Description ETC is universal platform for payments
- Techs: Microservice architecture with .NET Core 2, Entity Framework, RabbitMQ and MassTransit, React Native and SQL Server

CERTIFICATES

App Builder — Certified 2019

Microsoft

聞 Jan 2019 — No Expiration Date

Web Applications — Certified 2019

Microsoft

🛗 Jan 2019 — No Expiration Date

EDUCATION

B.Sc. in Physics and Informatics

Prirodoslovno – matematički fakultet Split, University of Split, Faculty of Science

Thesis title: Sending messages with a quantum signature

LANGUAGES

English



OTHERS

· Driving License – B